[{"answer": "Look, we started off the day this morning with a rough night in Asia.", "docId": "110818pmt", "aSentId": 14, "question": "What the hell is going on, Ali?", "qSentId": 13}, {"answer": "It is.", "docId": "110818pmt", "aSentId": 28, "question": "Is this looking more likely now, do you think?", "qSentId": 27}, {"answer": "It absolutely is.", "docId": "110818pmt", "aSentId": 39, "question": "Is this then a crisis caused by politics rather than straightforward economics?", "qSentId": 38}, {"answer": "After this.", "docId": "110818pmt", "aSentId": 63, "question": "When do you sleep?", "qSentId": 62}, {"answer": "Well, you shouldn't be afraid if you are sticking around for the long-term.", "docId": "110818pmt", "aSentId": 68, "question": "What should people be doing right now?", "qSentId": 67}, {"answer": "Well, I think the most obvious thing he can do is something about jobs.", "docId": "110818pmt", "aSentId": 130, "question": "If the Feds run out of bullets, what does the president have in his locker that he can do that is dramatic enough to stop this market mayhem?", "qSentId": 129}, {"answer": "There would have to be spending.", "docId": "110818pmt", "aSentId": 143, "question": "But, Leigh, wouldn't that mean that the president actually would have to -- it would have to be another stimulus, right?", "qSentId": 142}, {"answer": "I think that we need to focus on spending.", "docId": "110818pmt", "aSentId": 152, "question": "Neel, first to you?", "qSentId": 151}, {"answer": "Unfortunately, Neel's right.", "docId": "110818pmt", "aSentId": 158, "question": "Ali, what do you think?", "qSentId": 157}, {"answer": "Well, I'm running for the presidency of the United States.", "docId": "110818pmt", "aSentId": 176, "question": "And is it something that is conducted at the center?", "qSentId": 175}, {"answer": "I'm not being weird about this, Piers.", "docId": "110818pmt", "aSentId": 186, "question": "Why are you being so weird about this?", "qSentId": 185}, {"answer": "Not really, no.", "docId": "110818pmt", "aSentId": 199, "question": "Well, don't you think as a host, if I say this is what I want to talk about, that's what we should address?", "qSentId": 198}, {"answer": "Well, I was supposed to be speaking at the Republican women's club at 6:00, and I chose to be a little late for that, not to be -- you know, yes, not to endure rude talk show hosts, but to talk to you about my book and to talk about the issues that I address in my book.", "docId": "110818pmt", "aSentId": 207, "question": "You're leaving?", "qSentId": 206}, {"answer": "Yes, but these issues are in your book.", "docId": "110818pmt", "aSentId": 209, "question": "Have you read the book?", "qSentId": 208}, {"answer": "He's still there.", "docId": "110818pmt", "aSentId": 216, "question": "Are we done?", "qSentId": 215}, {"answer": "I thought your questions are perfectly fine.", "docId": "110818pmt", "aSentId": 229, "question": "Or was I behaving in a perfectly irresponsible journalistic manner?", "qSentId": 228}, {"answer": "Well, I thought -- I thought it was fascinating that she managed to push back on you when you were asking these questions without making any effort to really try to dodge them.", "docId": "110818pmt", "aSentId": 265, "question": "Todd, what did you make of it?", "qSentId": 264}, {"answer": "Well, I'm running for the presidency of the United States.", "docId": "110818pmt", "aSentId": 279, "question": "And is it something that is conducted at that center?", "qSentId": 278}, {"answer": "Yes, I think that's absolutely true.", "docId": "110818pmt", "aSentId": 301, "question": "Todd, what do you think?", "qSentId": 300}, {"answer": "Not at all.", "docId": "110818pmt", "aSentId": 317, "question": "Is there any doubt in your mind that you will be able to function in such circumstances?", "qSentId": 316}, {"answer": "We've had a bit of battles this week, as you may be aware.", "docId": "110818pmt", "aSentId": 337, "question": "A rock 'n' roll wild man, huh?", "qSentId": 336}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "110818pmt", "aSentId": 343, "question": "Have you ever walked out of an interview?", "qSentId": 342}, {"answer": "No, I would argue -- I mean, I would argue with you.", "docId": "110818pmt", "aSentId": 345, "question": "Could you imagine doing that?", "qSentId": 344}, {"answer": "I think I answered that question with the title of the album.", "docId": "110818pmt", "aSentId": 360, "question": "What do you make of what is happening to your country's economy?", "qSentId": 359}, {"answer": "It's all of the above.", "docId": "110818pmt", "aSentId": 369, "question": "Is it the politicians?", "qSentId": 368}, {"answer": "I think -- I think.", "docId": "110818pmt", "aSentId": 372, "question": "What do you think?", "qSentId": 371}, {"answer": "And I was working.", "docId": "110818pmt", "aSentId": 389, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 388}, {"answer": "Yeah, I'm fine.", "docId": "110818pmt", "aSentId": 395, "question": "Are you OK?", "qSentId": 394}, {"answer": "Yeah, probably have to slow down a little bit.", "docId": "110818pmt", "aSentId": 440, "question": "Time to slow down a little bit?", "qSentId": 439}, {"answer": "Around 43 million.", "docId": "110818pmt", "aSentId": 481, "question": "Do you know?", "qSentId": 480}, {"answer": "It hasn't made hardly any money for me.", "docId": "110818pmt", "aSentId": 486, "question": "Dare I ask how much money it has made you?", "qSentId": 485}, {"answer": "They declared me in breach of contract in 1982.", "docId": "110818pmt", "aSentId": 489, "question": "Why?", "qSentId": 488}, {"answer": "I think I got a check last week for 1.29.", "docId": "110818pmt", "aSentId": 493, "question": "So you sell 43 million copies of this album and barely made any money out of it?", "qSentId": 492}, {"answer": "No, I've made more because we -- we did take them to court at one point.", "docId": "110818pmt", "aSentId": 508, "question": "In total, have you made less than say a million dollars out of that?", "qSentId": 507}, {"answer": "When that -- and \"The Paradise,\" I was around 300, 310.", "docId": "110818pmt", "aSentId": 515, "question": "Did you really?", "qSentId": 514}, {"answer": "Well, I've gained seven pounds, so I'm sorry you asked me that.", "docId": "110818pmt", "aSentId": 517, "question": "What are you now?", "qSentId": 516}, {"answer": "A hundred and twenty, no.", "docId": "110818pmt", "aSentId": 525, "question": "What's your fighting weight?", "qSentId": 524}, {"answer": "EAT LOAF: I have no idea.", "docId": "110818pmt", "aSentId": 536, "question": "Do you know who you're going to vote for next election?", "qSentId": 535}, {"answer": "OK.", "docId": "110818pmt", "aSentId": 553, "question": "How did you end up at Meat Loaf?", "qSentId": 552}, {"answer": "No, I was called Meat.", "docId": "110818pmt", "aSentId": 565, "question": "You were still called Marvin at the time?", "qSentId": 564}, {"answer": "I had Meat Loaf on my passport when we first were touring \"Bat Out of Hell.\"", "docId": "110818pmt", "aSentId": 577, "question": "Are you now legally called Meat Loaf?", "qSentId": 576}, {"answer": "Michael Lee Aday.", "docId": "110818pmt", "aSentId": 582, "question": "What is on your passport?", "qSentId": 581}, {"answer": "Yes, since 1984.", "docId": "110818pmt", "aSentId": 584, "question": "So that's your -- you go by that name legally?", "qSentId": 583}, {"answer": "Meat.", "docId": "110818pmt", "aSentId": 587, "question": "Do you like to be called Mr. Loaf?", "qSentId": 586}, {"answer": "Yeah.", "docId": "110818pmt", "aSentId": 589, "question": "Meat?", "qSentId": 588}, {"answer": "It was at practice, but it was 62 feet with a 12- pound shot.", "docId": "110818pmt", "aSentId": 621, "question": "You were struck on the head with a shot during a shot put event?", "qSentId": 620}, {"answer": "Yeah.", "docId": "110818pmt", "aSentId": 624, "question": "Seriously?", "qSentId": 623}, {"answer": "Yes, Wolf Parkinson White.", "docId": "110818pmt", "aSentId": 637, "question": "A compliment?", "qSentId": 636}, {"answer": "I'm very lucky.", "docId": "110818pmt", "aSentId": 647, "question": "Are you very unlucky or are you very lucky, because you're still alive?", "qSentId": 646}, {"answer": "Christine O'Donnell.", "docId": "110818pmt", "aSentId": 667, "question": "If you could vote for anyone right now, who would it be?", "qSentId": 666}, {"answer": "Chris Christie, governor of New Jersey.", "docId": "110818pmt", "aSentId": 672, "question": "Who's that?", "qSentId": 671}, {"answer": "I'm not being weird.", "docId": "110818pmt", "aSentId": 686, "question": "Why are you being so weird about this?", "qSentId": 685}, {"answer": "And if you're going, go.", "docId": "110818pmt", "aSentId": 691, "question": "Where are you going?", "qSentId": 690}, {"answer": "Larry, you're being inappropriate.", "docId": "110818pmt", "aSentId": 695, "question": "Are we off?", "qSentId": 694}, {"answer": "I'm not going to talk about --", "docId": "110818pmt", "aSentId": 697, "question": "What?", "qSentId": 696}, {"answer": "It's the weirdest interview you'll ever see.", "docId": "110818pmt", "aSentId": 716, "question": "What's your question?", "qSentId": 715}, {"answer": "Kiss front man Gene Simmons was being interviewed with his significant other of 28 years when Joy Behar brought up his claim that he slept with 5,000 women.", "docId": "110818pmt", "aSentId": 719, "question": "What sent Fergie complete economy off the rails?", "qSentId": 718}]